sylvain forest on youtube facebook and dyango
youtube Facebook和dyango上的西尔万·森林（Sylvain Forest）
this speech is the flight home [Music]
这个演讲是回家的航班[音乐]
create and vice lightbox of laws [Music]
创建法律副灯箱[音乐]
edward darley in trouble
爱德华·达利陷入困境
dislike is to click arrows at this level
不喜欢单击此级别的箭头
their dress should also manatees [Music]
他们的衣服也应该是海牛[音乐]
tishman hashish cfe action taiwo written linked me captcha
提什曼大麻cfe动作台湾写链接我验证码
the stage fest
舞台巨星
[Music] i
[音乐]我
this no longer from felix takes holder
这不再来自费利克斯的持有人
so that it has dance of housing efe
这样就可以跳舞
[Applause]
[掌声]
Sure
当然
tim cook will and kate heinemann hash fields
蒂姆·库克·威廉姆斯和凯特·海涅曼哈希字段
transporting them out of the water is a complicated process that produces stress to
将它们从水中运出是一个复杂的过程，会产生压力
They are going to you is and that is why it is important to do it in the shortest time
他们要去找你，这就是为什么在最短的时间内做到这一点很重要的原因
possible we developed a system to adapt manatees in
我们可能开发了一个系统来适应海牛
some drawers and some containers in which they are totally tied to
一些抽屉和一些与它们完全绑在一起的容器
that they cannot move this means that we can reduce the risk that they
他们不能移动，这意味着我们可以减少他们
can be hit or hurt on the move
可能在移动中受到打击或伤害
lake univision on radioshack widget for coldplay cultivation
universal上的radioshack小部件进行感冒游戏培养
for javier de interaction huila vivo esquites effects
促进互动，惠拉体内产生效果
it's no use rescuing twenty fifty hundred manatees if people follow you
如果有人跟着你，救下两千五百只海牛是没有用的
unfortunately killing people in the Amazon has an ancestral culture of
不幸的是，在亚马逊杀死人有一种古老的文化
generation after generation of wildlife consumption and animal use
一代又一代的野生动植物消费和动物利用
As pets in the home, the work of changing the
作为家中的宠物，
minds of adults who have been raised that way but it is
以这种方式成长的成年人的思想，但这是
exceptionally exciting to see that work does work with children
看到工作确实对孩子有用，这让我异常兴奋
children have now become our main allies in the
现在，孩子们已成为我们在世界各地的主要盟友
conservation and the manatee has become an exceptional ally
保护和海牛已成为一个特殊的盟友
has a late chin
下巴晚了
really when children do not know has much
真的，当孩子不知道有多少
interest in finding out about the manatee find out what is happening to it what is its
寻找海牛的兴趣找出发生了什么事
problem and how they can help the manatee and that is how to date we have
问题，以及他们如何帮助海牛，这就是迄今为止的日期
released 23 mana 10 [Music]
释放23法力10 [音乐]
we make a promise to every fan and rescue
我们向每一个粉丝承诺并营救
That promise is that we will take care of you, we will feed you, we will protect you and
我们的承诺是，我们将照顾您，我们将养活您，我们将保护您，并
when the time comes we will set you free
时间到了，我们会让您自由
and we have kept that promise 23 times and we are very proud of
我们信守诺言23次，我们为此感到自豪
that [Music]
那个[音乐]
I hope you find many friends that I live was that
我希望你能找到很多我住的朋友是